{"data":[{"question":"By the end of the month I will ______ two books.","a":"have read","b":"be read","c":"had read","d":"be reading","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the end of this month","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Do vou think your mother will ______ dinner by now?","a":"have cook","b":"has cook","c":"have cooked","d":"has cooked","answer":"3","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by now","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"By the end of the month I'll ______ all my money,","a":"have spend","b":"have spent","c":"had spent","d":"had spend","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by the end of the month","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Our teacher will ______ correcting by 5 o'clock.","a":"have finish","b":"had finished","c":"had finish","d":"have finished","answer":"4","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by 5 o'clock","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"By nine o'clock the match ______.","a":"will have finished","b":"will finish","c":"has finish","d":"is finished","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by nine o'clock","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you think they'll ______ the invoice by now?","a":"send","b":"have sent","c":"have send","d":"be sending","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by now","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"By tomorrow he _____ his mind.","a":"is changing","b":"will have changed","c":"will be changing","d":"will change","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by tomorrow","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"By midnight I'll  ______ sleeping for two hours.","a":"have he","b":"have been","c":"had be","d":"had been","answer":"2","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by midnight","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I'll ______ the article before midnight.","a":"have wrote","b":"have write","c":"have written","d":"had written","answer":"3","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: before midnight","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"By seven o'clock they ______ dinner.","a":"will have already finished","b":"already will have finished","c":"will already had finished","d":"will already had finish","answer":"1","explain":"\nFuture perfect:\n+ Expresses the idea that something will occur before another action in the future. It can also show that something will happen before a specific time in the future\n+ Structure: S+ will\/shall +have+PP\n+ Sign word: by seven o'clock","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"21","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}